# Akash Verma



linkedin.com/in/akash-verma-18135008



https://getakash.com



akashverma.mec18@itbhu.ac.in



7054443300

# Summary

I'm passionate about learning the latest and greatest technologies weather thats the frontend or backend. I enjoy creating sleek and responsive applications in addition to being user friendly. I love working in fast paced environments. With my cultural and sport experiences I excel at collaborating with teams of same or different knowledge sets. A versatile engineer with interests in software Engineering and Algorithms. A sportsman and a Boxer. Adaptable and self motivated learner. Interested in new programming technologies, and continuous self improvement. I am currently open to opportunities within the software engineering discipline and if you feel like we would be a great match, I'd love to hear from you!

# Experience



#### Festival Coordinator

Mechanical Engineering Society, IIT - BHU, Varanasi Apr 2019 - Apr 2019 (1 month)



## Junior Coach(Full-stack dev..)

Unschool Jul 2020 - Present (1 month +)

### **Education**



#### Indian Institute of Technology (Banaras Hindu University), Varanasi

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Mechanical Engineering 2018 - 2022

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Web Design: Wireframes to Prototypes - Coursera

MMJ2E5YHDSP9

Web Design: Strategy and Information Architecture - Coursera

M5CTX3YHMXPJ

The Web Developer Bootcamp - Udemy

UC-6a58bc5b-73d0-4be1-a616-e19b332f5a02

**Advanced CSS and SASS** - Udemy, Inc.

UC-1d016949-c5bd-44c4-ae35-ee443e59ce4f

Algorithm Toolbox - Coursera

L7QWM6QK8DZA

#### Skills

HTML5 • JavaScript • Node.js • React.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • jQuery • Semantic UI • MongoDB • Mongoose ODM